[music]
>> Oh, hey. Hi. How are you? Welcome. When
did you get here? Anyway, doesn't
matter. I'm glad you're here.
First time here? My name's Fiddlin'
John. It's my fiddle channel and magic
product review. And today, we are
reviewing Joel Anthony's Hung, Drawn,
and Quartered Reimagined.
Now, there's other things out there that
get lots of hype. Many things that fly a
little bit under the radar screen.
So, let me put this on your radar
screen.
Let's get right into the review.
All right, let's go ahead and talk about
Hung, Drawn, and Quartered Reimagined by
Joel Anthony.
I'm going to go on a little bit of a
binge here for a second. Feel like
certain products right now are just
super hyped.
And maybe it's deserved.
I think one of them this week
Oh, now I'm forgetting the name of it.
But it feels like it's everywhere. And
certain products just get really hyped,
while other ones kind of
come out rather quietly. Maybe doesn't
get quite the promotion as some other
ones. And I feel like this is one of
them. It may be running under your radar
screen. Not for everybody. But it will
be, I think, some people's cup of tea
and will be really interesting to them.
All right, enough of that. Ranting about
like certain products get lots of
attention, while others go simply
invisible. And I want to make sure some
things get on your radar screen. All
right, Hung, Drawn, and Quartered
Reimagined by Joel Anthony. What is it?
It's actually technically not a first
release. It's actually the reimagined.
So, it's the 2.0 version. I don't think
it was all that long ago, maybe 2 years
ago,
if that, uh that the original was uh
released. This is an updated version
with more routines on it, um which I do
think uh improves, it gives you more
options.
What is it? At the core, it is card to
impossible location. And the specifics
in this one is card to signed card to uh
key ring. Um
and that your card ends up on a key
ring. Um I'll go through uh the other
variations here shortly. But that is the
core card to
uh impossible location. Uh but you can
also do color-changing card with it. You
can do a printing card with it where it
shows blank and then make it printed.
Um and uh yeah, that's sort of the the
essence of it. All right, let's talk
about
in this little package, what are you
going to get? All right, so um you're
going to get
two key rings, and they're very specific
key rings. They are flat key rings. I'm
only showing you one of them
uh here because I think the other one is
next to where I keep the rest of my
keys. Uh but they come in two different
sizes, and they come in two different
sizes specifically for different like
finger sizes. So that as you perform it,
it's usually done while um holding the
card on your finger. And if you got big
fat sausage fingers,
you have the bigger one so it fits your
fingers. Almost doesn't matter because
if you don't like it, just go out and
buy one that fits your fat sausage
fingers. Uh but I think for most folks,
the it'll be just fine. If it matters to
folks, one is 25 mm, and the other is 28
mm.
All right. So you're going to get uh two
of those uh
uh
finger rings. Uh you're going to get 20
pre-prepared
uh and I'll tell you up front
pre-scored cards. So, you're going to
get 20 uh
Bicycle Rider Back blue and red uh
cards. Don't imagine they're going to
come pre-hole punched, so you don't have
to hole-punch them. And they'll come
scored because you'll do I'll just
reveal part of it. You're going to be
doing Well, if you know that they have
to be scored,
um you might be able to figure it out.
So, um
that's what you're getting. Re- regular
cards that you could do all the
gimmicking yourself, quite frankly. So,
that when you are done with these, it
doesn't matter. Just use
uh your other cards and do the same and
you are good to go. They are consumable,
though, because
each performance, essentially, a card
gets signed and destroyed. Um you
wouldn't use it after that. Uh it is a
handout, and so uh just know that it's
that type of a uh release. Okay.
Still talking about what are you going
to get?
Um Okay, and you're also going to get um
let's see. You're going to get a total
of four gimmicks um that are two red and
two blue card gimmicks.
Um And in essence, of the four, two of
them
are gimmicked in a certain way. And so,
um just know that. It's pretty
straightforward uh gimmicks that are
there.
Okay, so you're going to get those four
gimmicked cards
and those four gimmicked cards are the
ones that go on your keychain. Um all
right, and you're also, probably most
importantly, the uh downloadable video,
which is on Vimeo, and it is 48 minutes
in length. All right, that's what you're
getting. Your consumables, uh your
gimmicks, etc. How is the tutorial? It's
good. Is it amazing? Fantastic? Out of
this world? No, but it's good. It does
the job. It is taught by Joe Anthony, uh
the creator of these routines, uh and he
does a great job. It's multi-camera and
uh paced perfectly. And at 48 minutes,
you get all that you need to be able to
uh per- to perform it. So, simple as
that.
Um let me talk about what are the
specific routines that are taught on it
uh and it. So, you're going to get four
routines. There's a confabulation, and
I'll read some of the ad copy for you
It's a confabulation. It's a fantastic
confabulation routine for the mentalist
out there. Use your own very own
business card and have a prediction
ready and pierced on your keyring that
matches the spectator's
word or picture. The other one that's uh
taught is the Chicago drawn and
quartered. Basically, it's Joel's take
on the Chicago style opener, where the
back of the signed card changes color
before turning completely blank and
their card appearing on your keyring.
There's the original, which is uh Joel's
own drawn and quartered routine, where
the signed card is pierced on your
keyring and it's ripped off to be handed
out to the spectator. And the final one
is the color changes. Show a prediction
on your keyring that is the wrong color
card with a different back design, wave
your hand over it, change the card to
match the deck, and rip it off to show
your spectator's signed card. Those are
all really solid routines. Those are
worker routines, I think, for those who
are workers and uh probably doing
walk-around or close-up style. Um
They're solid solid uh effects and
time-tested. All right, uh let's talk
about Normally, I would talk about how
is the gimmick? There's not much to say
here other than they're standard Bicycle
cards that have been pre-hole punched
for you and scored.
Um
you're getting the keyrings. Um there is
something special about one of the
keyrings, but you can just go to your
local hardware store and purchase
another one if you lost it or wanted a
different size. And let's see.
I think that's it. There's nothing like,
will this last or anything.
They're basically cards and key rings.
Nothing else.
Well, a little bit with the
with one of them, but it's insignificant
to even mention. All right, so the
takeaway, gimmicks are fine, okay?
What's the skill level?
I say this a lot, but I mean it strongly
with this one. This is a beginner level,
but does require practice for it to look
good.
You're not going to be able to get it,
and you could start performing it right
away, but I would say put in a little
bit of practice time to just get your
card graph moves looking really nice.
Let's go over sort of the stuff like, if
I were you and I was sitting on that
side of the screen, what would I care
about? So, the first thing I'll say is
like, if you like EDC, everyday carry,
this is great for the casual performer.
In fact, I
This is my regular key ring that I use
everyday. It's got a what do you call
it, carabiner on it, and then I just
keep my card
on its key ring, attach it to the
carabiner on the rest of my
key chain, and I'm ready to go. And I
just throw this into my pocket. I
sometimes think, oh, this is getting
really beaten up. So far, so good. And I
keep this in my pocket all day. And then
some days if I don't want to, I just
simply pull it off of here, and um
don't need to bring it with me. So,
it's my long-winded way of saying it's
great everyday carry
with you. All you need then is your own
deck of cards to carry with you, and
you're all you are good to go.
I will talk about what the negative
thing is here. And this is really me and
my experience, and others may
[clears throat] not have this same or
shared experience. There's a move that
happens,
and the move is where essentially the
magic happens. As a magician, I don't
think I can help but look at it and go,
"Oh, there's the move. That's when it's
happening." Um, I
feel a little awkward doing the move,
quite honestly, because my magician
brain goes, "There is no way in heck I'm
going to get away with this." And to be
frank,
I look clumsy doing it. It's one of the
reasons I didn't put up a demo of it,
and maybe I'll have already put up or
will put up um the trailer for it uh or
pieces of it. But, um
I feel clumsy doing it, and sometimes I
don't want to put stuff up if it's just
too obvious. Um, and I'm doing it
clumsy. And the truth is, I kind of do
it a little bit clumsy. Um, will Muggles
notice it?
No. It My own experience shows like when
I have moves like this, and I think
there's no way I'm going to get away
with it,
I do.
The regular public, non-magicians, don't
know these moves. They don't understand
what's happening. There might be some go
like, "I think that's where something
happened." But, they wouldn't know
[clears throat] anything past that. So,
I I say that just to share what my own
experience is.
Um,
the for magicians, you'll see the move a
mile away. Um, but it shouldn't dissuade
you, I think, from consideration
um of it because the effects are really
solid effects. They are workers, in
fact. So,
um it's not the sort of effect I'm
honestly going to be performing on a
regular basis, mostly because it's not
exactly my style. Yeah, I do carry it
with me. Uh so that when opportunity
arises, I'm ready to go. But, I probably
won't be performing it on a regular
basis, but I know others who will
immediately look at this and go, "Oh,
that fits me perfectly."
And um will be no issues for them. So,
um this is where I would say, "Watch the
trailer."
The trailer's are very accurate. If you
like what you see um and how it looks,
it's well worth consideration. So,
but I do want to say that like just off
the top of my head, like I see the
movement and I'm like,
"Golly, that'll be noticed from a mile
away." And I'm always wrong on that. All
right.
I think I
probably already said it. This is a
really good It's a good close-up piece.
It resets in seconds. If you're doing
walk around in particular
and you're gigging with it, easy from
one table to the next to reset. Nobody
sees anything.
Literally in seconds.
And also one of the nice things about
this, you don't have to switch out for
another deck. Just continue using it
once you've done this effect and you
want to perform more card effects,
you're using a regular deck. So,
continue with your regular card effects
with it. If you don't like signed card
routines as the way to prove stuff,
maybe this isn't for you. But the nice
thing is you can have them sign the card
and the signed card is what will
give you the appearance of coming off
the key ring and handing right back to
them.
There's no bad angles on this at all.
And it's nice at the end, you pretty
much end clean. You hand them their
signed card, you hand them the deck of
cards and they can fully examine all of
those. At this point, of course, I put
away my key ring, but um
yeah,
there's nothing for them to see. So,
it's nice in that respect. All right,
how much does this cost? This costs $35.
I think that's a very reasonable price
for the consumables that you're getting
here. Could it be a download? Yes, this
could be a download only and then you
could get the consumables yourself. I
personally like that they include it at
least for the at least the first round
for you. Like I've got 20 performances
that are right out of the box ready to
go before I need to go into my own cards
Uh, and use the decks that I use to
destroy cards while performing. So,
um
where can you get it? You can it's
produced by uh, Pocket Miracles, but
it's available through any Murphy's
Magic retailer. You can get it at
Penguin.
You can get it at Alakazam. So, you
should be able to get this at most of
your major magic retailers. Um, all
right. That's it. I hope this was
helpful. I want today to bring something
that may not be on your radar screen
that hasn't had the hype behind it like
other
effects are because you're getting
something new and fancy gimmick. This is
just good solid magic with everyday
objects that you would carry with you.
And the effects are solid. Simple as
that.
Um,
the only thing I don't like is the one
move, but um, that's because I've got
magician thinking going on. Outside
that, I think it's a really good
product. All right. Thank you so much
for watching everyone. I really do
appreciate it. Make sure that you leave
a comment down below if you have the
original or this one, what you think of
it, maybe something I missed in it. Uh,
hit that subscribe button if you haven't
yet subscribed. Thank you for all the
subscribers. I really appreciate it. I'd
love to boost up the number of
subscribers I have cuz it helps with the
algorithm. And at bare minimum, it is
free to hit that like button. If you
could hit that like button, I really
genuinely would appreciate it. Again, it
just helps the channel. I know we all
say that on YouTube. But we really do
appreciate it. I know I do. All right.
Thank you so much for being here. I'm
Fiddlin Johnny and remember to keep
fiddlin around with your magic. I'll see
you all next time. Bye-bye.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Oh.